<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<ModMetaData>
	<name>[KV] RimFridge - 1.1</name>
	<author>Kiame Vivacity</author>
	<supportedVersions>
        <li>1.0</li>
        <li>1.1</li>
	</supportedVersions>

	<url>https://ludeon.com/forums/index.php?topic=32980.0</url>
	<description>Adds refrigerated racks to keep food and other perishables cold.  Ideal for use in dining rooms, freeing up labour from feeding prisoners, or keeping food on hand for cooks.

Base RimFridge comes in 1x1, 1x2, and 2x2 versions.  A "Wall" version of the 1x1 and 1x2 can be used to divide rooms and seperate the kitchen from the dining area, or create hard, impassible aisles of freezers.  Wall RimFridges are accessible by pawns from both sides.

Beer and some other alcohols such as RimCusine 2's Stout, Ale, Grog and Cider gain a "Frosty" moodlet if chilled in a RimFridge and drunk by a colonist, because who doesn't like a cold one after a long day's work?  Additional items from other mods can be easilly added to the XML files in Defs\ThingDefs_Buildings.

A note to modders, this mod no longer destroys Rottables with its own version and all destructive prefixes were removed.  All code was moved to a ThingComp which can be attached onto any Building_Storage that has power to give it Refrigeration capabilities.  

Thanks to everyone who's helped translate this mod!
-Dragomano &amp; qeqwrqweqweter - Russian
-53N4 - Spanish
-duduluu &amp; Schr0d &amp; Jiunejai &amp; failucha - Chinese
-phmalu - Portuguese
-Breakyt - French
-Ɲơɴɑɱɛ - German
-KondenEinenShizainoLaw - Japanese
-silverjoy &amp; Orange_Mushroom - Korean
-drerp - Hungarian
-WebsterBolek - Polish
-Firty &amp; MrCaka - Portuguese / Brazilian

Thanks to everyone who's added/edited code!
-Demonseed Elite - Refactored code for better compatibility and additional features
-towhead - Made the fridges hide the uglyness of food

Original Author: Vendan</description>
<packageId>rimfridge.kv.rw</packageId>
<modDependencies>
    <li>
        <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
        <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
        <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
        <downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
    </li>
</modDependencies>
</ModMetaData>